{
    "subject": "resource/Felton_Covered_Bridge",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "The Felton Covered Bridge is a covered bridge over the San Lorenzo River in Felton, Santa Cruz County in the U.S. state of California. Built in 1892, the bridge employs a brown truss structural system and is approximately 80 feet long. The bridge became a California Historical Landmark in 1957, was placed on the National Register of Historic Places in 1973, and had a major restoration in 1987 after being damaged in storms in the winter of 1982. It is considered to be the tallest covered bridge in the United States, and was the main entry point for Felton for 45 years.The bridge is no longer used on the roadway, but is accessible to pedestrians visiting the Felton Covered Bridge Park.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of Felton Covered Bridge is that it's a covered bridge over the San Lorenzo River in Felton, Santa Cruz County in the U.S. state of California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.945663571357727,
            "question": "In which state is the Felton Covered Bridge situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9226865172386169,
            "question": "Which river does the Felton Covered Bridge cross?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208119511604309,
            "question": "Where is the Felton Covered Bridge located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9039914011955261,
            "question": "What type of structure is the Felton Covered Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.847947895526886,
            "question": "Is the Felton Covered Bridge a historical landmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8464586138725281,
            "question": "What county is home to the Felton Covered Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7654048204421997,
            "question": "Can you imagine what it would be like to travel over the Felton Covered Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5579585433006287,
            "question": "Are there any other covered bridges in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5225011110305786,
            "question": "What might be some reasons for building a covered bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.270701140165329,
            "question": "What is the significance of covered bridges in history and culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of Felton Covered Bridge is that it's a covered bridge over the San Lorenzo River in Felton, Santa Cruz County in the U.S. state of California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2927_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some reasons for building a covered bridge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2927_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other covered bridges in California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2927_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you imagine what it would be like to travel over the Felton Covered Bridge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2927_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2927_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that The abstract of Felton Covered Bridge is that it's a covered bridge over the San Lorenzo River in Felton, Santa Cruz County in the U.S. state of California. This statement can be found in multiple documents with the same file path, including:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2927/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2927/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Felton Covered Bridge, confirming that it is a covered bridge located over the San Lorenzo River in Felton, Santa Cruz County, in the U.S. state of California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}